<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Widget</string>
    <string name="my_name">Wadud Azad</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="about_android">Android is a mobile operating system developed by Google. It is based
        on a modified version of the Linux kernel and other open source software, and is designed
        primarily for touchscreen mobile devices such as smartphones and tablets. In addition, Google
        has further developed Android TV for televisions, Android Auto for cars, and Wear OS for
        wrist watches, each with a specialized user interface. Variants of Android are also used on
        game consoles, digital cameras, PCs and other electronics. hi Android primarily for touchscreen mobile devices such as smartphones and tablets
    </string>
    <string name="message">I am not supposing him at all an creature, in suspecting that he may have learnt to be above his connexions, and to care very little for any thing but his own pleasure, from living with those who have always set him the example of it. It is a great deal more natural than one could wish, that a young man, brought up by those who are proud, luxurious, and selfish, should be proud, luxurious, and selfish too. If Frank Churchill had wanted to see his father, he would have contrived it between September and January. A man at his age—what is he?—three or four-and-twenty—cannot be without the means of doing as much as that. It is impossible.’ ’That’s easily said, and easily felt by you, who have always been your own master. You are the worst judge in the world, Mr. Knightley, of the difficulties of dependence. You do not know what it is to have tempers to manage.’ ’It is not to be conceived that a man of three or four-and-twenty should not have liberty of mind or limb to that amount. He cannot want money—he cannot want leisure. We know, on the contrary, that he has so much of both, that he is glad to get rid of them at the idlest haunts in the kingdom. We hear of him for ever at some watering-place or other. A little while ago, he was at Weymouth. This proves that he can leave the Churchills.</string>

</resources>
